(car engine rumbles)
- One, two, three, four.
("Big Girls Don't Cry")
♪ Da da da da ♪
♪ The smell of your
skin lingers on me now ♪
♪ You're probably on your
flight back to your hometown ♪
♪ I need some shelter of
my own protection, baby ♪
♪ To be with myself and center ♪
♪ Clarity, peace, serenity ♪
♪ I hope you know, I hope you know ♪
♪ That this has nothing to do with you ♪
♪ It's personal, myself and I ♪
♪ We've got some straightening out to do ♪
♪ And I'm gonna miss you like
a child misses their blanket ♪
♪ But I've got to get a
move on with my life ♪
♪ It's time to be a big girl now ♪
♪ And big girls don't cry ♪
♪ Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ The path that I'm
walking, I must go alone ♪
♪ I must take the baby steps
till I'm full grown, full grown ♪
♪ Fairy tales don't always
have a happy ending, do they ♪
♪ And I foresee the dark ahead if I stay ♪
♪ I hope you know, I hope you know ♪
♪ That this has nothing to do with you ♪
♪ It's personal, myself and I ♪
♪ We've got some straightening out to do ♪
♪ And I'm gonna miss you like
a child misses their blanket ♪
♪ But I've got to get a
move on with my life ♪
♪ It's time to be a big girl now ♪
♪ And big girls don't cry ♪
♪ Like the little schoolmate
in the schoolyard ♪
♪ We'll play Jacks and Uno cards ♪
♪ I'll be your best friend,
and you'll be mine, Valentine ♪
♪ Yes, you can hold my
hand if you want to ♪
♪ 'Cause I want to hold yours too ♪
♪ We'll be playmates and lovers,
and share our secret worlds ♪
♪ But it's time for me to go home ♪
♪ It's getting late and dark outside ♪
♪ I need to be with myself and center ♪
♪ Clarity, peace, serenity, yeah ♪
♪ I hope you know, I hope you know ♪
♪ That this has nothing to do with you ♪
♪ It's personal, myself and I ♪
♪ We've got some straightening out to do ♪
♪ And I'm gonna miss you like
a child misses their blanket ♪
♪ But I've got to get a
move on with my life ♪
♪ It's time to be a big girl now ♪
♪ And big girls don't cry ♪
♪ Don't cry, don't cry, don't cry ♪
♪ La da da da da da ♪
(car engine rumbles)